Historical Materials Collection UA136
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
- Audio Lab materials, 1962 -- 2003; UA136.004; 8.4 Linear Feet; 1 Digital Object(s)
  - Rights of Animals, given by Professor Peter Singer, 1973-11-29; UA136.004.024.00096; Singer, Peter (Case 28)
    Department of Philosophy Colloquium
  - The Erosion of Civil Liberties, given by U.S. Representative Barbara Jordan, 1974-03-08; UA136.004.024.00097; Jordan, Barbara (Case 24)
    Conferral of Honorary Degree by President Hallowell
  - Obsolescence of Our World Systems, given by I.F. Stone, 1974-04-09; UA136.004.024.00098; Stone, I.F. (Case 24)
  - Rape, given by Barbara Short, 1974-04-22; UA136.004.024.00099; Short, Barbara (Case 24)
    Social Worker, Boston City Hospital. Health Education Lectures
  - Role of Business in American Society, given by Thomas Allsopp, 1974-04-25; UA136.004.024.00100; Allsopp, Thomas (Case 24)
  - Three Musicians: A Composite of Black Music, given by T.J. Anderson, 1974-04-25; UA136.004.024.00101; Anderson, T.J. (Case 24)
  - Nuclear Energy and Safety - S.O.A.P. and P.I.R.G. panel, 1974-04-29; UA136.004.024.00102 (Case 28)
  - Science and Politics of I.Q., given by Leon Kamin, 1 of 2, 1974-05-01; UA136.004.024.00103; Kamin, Leon (Case 24)
  - Science and Politics of I.Q., given by Leon Kamin, 2 of 2, 1974-05-01; UA136.004.024.00104; Kamin, Leon (Case 24)
  - State of the Black Liberation Movement, given by Bobby Seale, 1974-05-02; UA136.004.024.00105; Seale, Bobby (Case 24)
  - The Rosenberg Case, given by Morton Sobel, 1 of 2, 1974-05-07; UA136.004.024.00106; Sobel, Morton (Case 24, Case 28)
    Co-Speaker: M. Mirapol
  - The Rosenberg Case, given by Morton Sobel, 2 of 2, 1974-05-07; UA136.004.024.00107; Sobel, Morton (Case 24)
  - The African Revolution, given by Stokely Carmichael, 1 of 2, 1974-05-09; UA136.004.024.00108 (Case 24, Case 28)
  - The African Revolution, given by Stokely Carmichael, 2 of 2, 1974-05-09; UA136.004.024.00109 (Case 24)
  - Remarks, Retirement Dinner, given by Earl Littleton, 1974-05-11; UA136.004.024.00110; Littleton, Earl (Case 28)
  - Poetry Reading, given by George Beal, 1974-05-14; UA136.004.024.00111; Beal, George (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker: Geoffrey Movius
  - Poetry Reading, given by Geoffrey Movius, 1974-05-14; UA136.004.024.00112; Movius, Geoffrey (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker: George Beal
  - Women's Movement and Radical Feminism, given by Robin Morgan, 1 of 2, 1974-05-16; UA136.004.024.00113; Morgan, Robin (Case 24)
  - Women's Movement and Radical Feminism, given by Robin Morgan, 2 of 2, 1974-05-16; UA136.004.024.00114; Morgan, Robin (Case 24)
  - Perspectives in the Black Experience, given by Dr. Michael Lewis, 1974-05-16; UA136.004.024.00115; Lewis, Michael (Case 24)
  - Poetry Reading, given by Denise Levertov, 1974-05-21; UA136.004.024.00116; Levertov, Denise (Case 24)
  - Who Killed J.F.K.?, given by Harvey Yazieman, 1974-05-21; UA136.004.024.00117; Yazieman, Harvey (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker Dave Williams
  - Who Killed J.F.K.?, given by David Williams, 1974-05-21; UA136.004.024.00118; Williams, David (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker Harvey Yazieman
  - Remarks, Dental School Graduation, given by Noam Chomsky, 1974-06-01; UA136.004.024.00119; Chomsky, Noam (Case 24)
  - Attica, given by Ramsey Clark and Big Black, 1974-09-12; UA136.004.024.00120; Clark, Ramsey; Smith, Frank "Big Black" (Case 24, Case 28)
  - The Black Experience, given by Dr. James Turner, 1 of 2, 1974-09-19; UA136.004.024.00121; Turner, James Dr. (Case 24, Case 28)
  - The Black Experience, given by Dr. James Turner, 2 of 2, 1974-09-19; UA136.004.024.00122; Turner, James Dr. (Case 24)
  - Innateness Theory of Learning, given by Noam Chomsky, 1974-10-02; UA136.004.024.00123; Chomsky, Noam (Case 24)
  - The Art of Filmmaking, given by Robert Altman, 1974-10-03; UA136.004.024.00124; Altman, Robert (Case 28)
    Talk given by film director Robert Altman to the Tufts community titled 'The Art of Filmmaking'.
  - Eliot-Pearson Groundbreaking, given by Dr. Evelyn Pitcher and Burton C. Hallowell, 1974-10-09; UA136.004.024.00125; Pitcher, Evelyn; Hallowell, Burton (Case 28)
  - Earle Gettles Review-Benefit Coffeehouse music performances, 1974-11-01; UA136.004.024.00127 (Case 24, Case 29)
    Willie Nininger, Bill Gehling, Ross Dolloff
  - Vietnam, given by Daniel Ellsberg, 1974-11-08; UA136.004.024.00128; Ellsberg, Daniel (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: J. Fonda, H. Near
  - Vietnam, given by Jane Fonda, 1974-11-08; UA136.004.024.00129; Fonda, Jane (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: D. Ellsberg, H. Near
  - Vietnam, given by Holly Near, 1974-11-08; UA136.004.024.00130; Near, Holly (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: D. Ellsberg, J. Fonda
  - What were the Sixties?, given by Hugo Bedau, 1974-11-12; UA136.004.024.00131; Bedau, Hugo Adam (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: A. Schmidt, T. Glynn, P. Primack
  - What were the Sixties?, given by Tom Glynn, 1974-11-12; UA136.004.024.00132; Glynn, Tom (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: A. Schmidt, H. Bedau, P. Primack
  - What were the Sixties?, given by Phil Primack, 1974-11-12; UA136.004.024.00133 (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: A. Schmidt, H. Bedau, T. Glynn
  - What were the Sixties?, given by Alvin Schmidt, 1974-11-12; UA136.004.024.00134; Schmidt, Alvin (Case 24)
    Co-Speakers: T. Glynn, P.Primack, H. Bedau
  - World Food Crisis, given by Jeff Gibson, Donald Klein, and Dirck Stryker, 1974-11-21; UA136.004.024.00135; Gibson, Jeff; Klein, Donald; Stryker, Dirck (Case 28)
  - Politics, given by Julian Bond, 1974-11-25; UA136.004.024.00138; Bond, Julian (Case 24)
  - Israeli Theater, given by Gershon Shaked, 1 of 2, 1974-12-05; UA136.004.024.00139; Shaked, Gershon (Case 24, Case 29)
  - Israeli Theater, given by Gershon Shaked, 2 of 2, 1974-12-05; UA136.004.024.00140; Shaked, Gershon (Case 24)
  - On Myths, given by Rollo May, 1974-12-06; UA136.004.024.00141; May, Rollo (Case 24)
  - Macphie Dining Hall Benefit music performances, 1974-12-10; UA136.004.024.00142 (Case 24)
    Beelzebubs, Jills, Mitch Silver, Ed Bauman, Gwen and Friends
  - The Economy and You, given by James M. Howell, 1975-01-28; UA136.004.024.00143; Howell, James M. (Case 24)
    Economist, Bank of Boston
  - The Dynamics of a Liberal Arts Education, given by Mary Ella Feinleib, Seymour Simches, and Brenda Steinberg, 1975-02-18; UA136.004.024.00144; Feinleib, Mary Ella; Simches, Seymour; Steinberg, Brenda (Case 29)
  - Tufts Community Choir, Jackson Jills, Steve Gordon music performances, 1975-03-01; UA136.004.024.00147 (Case 28)
  - General and Autobiographical Remarks, given by Anthony Burgess, 1975-03-04; UA136.004.024.00148; Burgess, Anthony (Case 24, Case 28)
  - The Consumer's Right to be Heard, given by Carol Goldberg, 1975-04-03; UA136.004.024.00149; Goldberg, Carol (Case 28)
    Alumna; General Manager, Stop and Shop.
  - Third World Task Force panel, 1975-04-10; UA136.004.024.00151 (Case 24, Case 29)
  - Remarks, given by Juan Carlos Coral, 1975-04-15; UA136.004.024.00152; Coral, Juan Carlos (Case 28)
  - U.S. Foreign Policy After Vietnam, given by U.S. Senator Tom Clarke, 1975-04-16; UA136.004.024.00153; Clarke, Tom (Case 24)
    Democrat, Iowa
  - Intercollegiate Sing music performances, 1975-04-17; UA136.004.024.00154 (Case 24)
  - Remarks on American Society, given by Dick Gregory, 1975-04-20; UA136.004.024.00155; Gregory, Dick (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
  - Politics and Media, given by Dan Rather, 1975-04-24; UA136.004.024.00156; Rather, Dan (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
    Introduced by Professor Donald Klein
  - Cambridge Controversy and the Theory of Capital, given by G.C. Harcourt, 1975-04-30; UA136.004.024.00157; Harcourt, G. C. (Case 24)
  - The Stroboscopic World, given by M.E. Edgerton, 1975-05-08; UA136.004.024.00158; Edgerton, M. E. (Case 24)
  - The Press, given by Seymour Hirsch, 1975-09-11; UA136.004.024.00159; Hirsch, Seymour (Case 24)
  - Lecture given by Isaac Asimov, 1975-09-11; UA136.004.024.00160; Asimov, Isaac (Case 28)
  - Humor, given by P.J. O'Rourke, 1975-10-21; UA136.004.024.00161; O'Rourke, P.J. (Case 24)
    Executive Editor, National Lampoon
  - Beelzebubs and Jackson Jills music performances, 1975-12-03; UA136.004.024.00162 (Case 24)
    Goddard Chapel
  - Science Fiction Writer as Prophet, given by Isaac Asimov, 1975-12-09; UA136.004.024.00163; Asimov, Isaac (Case 24)
  - Presidential Campaign Issues, given by Jimmy Carter, 1975-12-09; UA136.004.024.00164; Carter, Jimmy (Case 24)
  - Presidential Campaign Issues, given by U.S. Senator Birch Bayh, 1976-02-28; UA136.004.024.00165; Bayh, Birch (Case 24)
  - Presidential Press Conference, given by Jean Mayer, 1976-03-22; UA136.004.024.00166; Mayer, Jean (Case 24)
  - Feminism and Fertility, given by Germaine Greer, 1976-03-26; UA136.004.024.00167; Greer, Germaine (Case 24)
    Tufts Lecture Series
  - The Search For God in Modern Culture, given by William Edgar, 1976-04-01; UA136.004.024.00168; Edgar, William (Case 24)
    Editor, Genesis. Tufts Christian Fellowship Lecture
  - Medical and Legal Ethics, given by Harold Brown, 1976-04-08; UA136.004.024.00169; Brown, Harold (Case 24)
    Tufts Christian Fellowship Lecture
  - American Revolutionary Tradition and the World, given by Gordon Wood, 1976-04-12; UA136.004.024.00170; Wood, Gordon (Case 24)
    Tufts Alumnus; Faculty Member, Brown University
  - Art Between Nirvana and Technology, given by Jonathan Bragdon, 1976-04-20; UA136.004.024.00171; Bragdon, Jonathan (Case 24)
  - Tufts Presidential Inauguration, given by Jean Mayer, 1976-09-18; UA136.004.024.00172; Mayer, Jean (Case 24)
  - Consumer and Social Issues, given by Ralph Nader, 1 of 2, 1976-10-07; UA136.004.024.00173; Nader, Ralph (Case 24)
  - Consumer and Social Issues, given by Ralph Nader, 2 of 2, 1976-10-07; UA136.004.024.00174; Nader, Ralph (Case 24)
  - Campaign Issues, given by U.S. Senator Edward M. Kennedy, 1976-10-14; UA136.004.024.00175; Kennedy, Edward M. (Case 24)
    Introduction by Jean Mayer
  - Counterculture from 1945 to 1985, given by Timothy Leary, 1 of 2, 1976-10-15; UA136.004.024.00176; Leary, Timothy (Case 24)
  - Counterculture from 1945 to 1985, given by Timothy Leary, 2 of 2, 1976-10-15; UA136.004.024.00176a; Leary, Timothy (Case 28)
  - Political Involvement, given by U.S. Representative Bella Abzug, 1976-12-08; UA136.004.024.00177; Abzug, Bella (Case 24)
  - The Emergence of Party in World Politics, given by Daniel P. Moynihan, 1976-12-15; UA136.004.024.00178; Moynihan, Daniel P. (Case 24)
    Introduction by Dean Edmund Gullion
  - Black Women Speak panel, 1977-01-31; UA136.004.024.00179 (Case 24)
    Moderator: Patricia Hall. Women's Week at Tufts.
  - What is Feminist Therapy panel, 1977-02-01; UA136.004.024.00180 (Case 24)
    Mimi Elmer, Carol Lambert, et al. Women's Week at Tufts
  - Comedy, given by Robert Klein, 1977-02-11; UA136.004.024.00181; Klein, Robert (Case 24)
    Produced by Beezebubs. Tufts Lecture Series.
  - Comedy, given by Robert Klein, 1977-02-11; UA136.004.024.00182; Klein, Robert (Case 24)
    Preceded by Beelzebubs. Tufts Lecture Series.
  - Intellectuals in Contemporary Spanish Politics, given by Juan Marechal, 1977-03-02; UA136.004.024.00183; Marechal, Juan (Case 24)
    Professor of Spanish, Harvard University
  - Remarks, given by F. Lee Bailey, 1977-03-24; UA136.004.024.00184; Bailey, F. Lee (Case 24)
  - Gender and Occupation, given by Margaret Mead, 1977-04-07; UA136.004.024.00185; Mead, Margaret (Case 24)
  - Women's Role in Social and Economic Development, given by Helvi Sipila, 1977-04-14; UA136.004.024.00186; Sipila, Helvi (Case 24)
    United Nations Representative for Women
  - Obscenity Laws and First Amendment Rights, given by Harry Reems, 1977-04-20; UA136.004.024.00187; Reems, Harry (Case 24)
  - Theater in Quebec, given by Michel Tremblay, 1977-04-25; UA136.004.024.00188; Tremblay, Michel (Case 24)
  - Humor, given by David Frye, 1977-09-29; UA136.004.024.00189; Frye, David (Case 24)
  - Readings from her Book: Letters, A Family Self Portrait, given by Dr. Jesse Bernard, 1977-10-13; UA136.004.024.00190; Bernard, Jesse Dr. (Case 24)
    Mellon Grant Lecture
  - Remarks on his Writings, given by Julio Cortazar, 1977-10-17; UA136.004.024.00191; Cortazar, Julio (Case 24)
    In Spanish
  - Women and the Law: Marriage, Property and Divorce, given by Evelyn Ellis, 1977-10-18; UA136.004.024.00192; Ellis, Evelyn (Case 24)
  - Debate with Phyllis Schlafley, given by Karen Decroe, 1977-10-27; UA136.004.024.00193; Decroe, Karen (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker: Phyllis Schlafley
  - Debate with Karen Decroe, given by Phyllis Schlafley, 1977-10-27; UA136.004.024.00194; Schlafley, Phyllis (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker: Karen Decroe. Tufts Lecture Series.
  - Women and the Law: Rape and Women, given by Judith Mears, 1977-11-01; UA136.004.024.00195; Mears, Judith (Case 24)
  - Adolescent Sexuality, given by Dr. Kenneth Edelin, 1977-11-09; UA136.004.024.00196; Edelin, Kenneth Dr. (Case 24)
  - Women and the Law: Abortion, given by Judith Mears, 1977-11-10; UA136.004.024.00197; Mears, Judith (Case 24)
  - Tufts Alums Discuss Business School panel, 1977-11-15; UA136.004.024.00198 (Case 24)
  - Everest Adventure, given by Woodrow Wilson Sayre, 1977-11-16; UA136.004.024.00199; Sayre, Woodrow Wilson (Case 24)
  - Interview on Physics, given by Professor Weisskopf, 1977-12-02; UA136.004.024.00200 (Case 24)
  - National Security Policy, given by Richard Burt, 1977-12-04; UA136.004.024.00201; Burt, Richard (Case 24)
    New York Times National Security Reporter
  - Revolutionary Tradition in Afro-American Literature, given by Amiri Baraka, 1978-03-08; UA136.004.024.00202; Baraka, Amiri (Case 24)
  - L'Art du Roman, given by Nathalie Sarraute, 1978-03-28; UA136.004.024.00203; Sarraute, Nathalie (Case 24)
    In French
  - Tufts in Paris Program panel, 1978-04-04; UA136.004.024.00204 (Case 24)
    Director Of Tufts In Paris and French native.
  - Tufts Priory, given by Jean Mayer, 1978-09-10; UA136.004.024.00205; Mayer, Jean (Case 28)
  - European-American Intellectual Exchanges in 20th Century, given by Stephen Graubard, 1978-09-26; UA136.004.024.00206; Graubard, Stephen (Case 24)
    History Lecture Series
  - Conceptions of Time and Space, Europe & America 1880-1915, given by Stephen Kern, 1978-10-05; UA136.004.024.00207; Kern, Stephen (Case 24)
  - Protest without Confrontation, given by Michael Adas, 1978-10-24; UA136.004.024.00208; Adas, Michael (Case 24)
  - Who was Tutankhamen?, given by Alexander Kaczmarczyk, 1978-10-24; UA136.004.024.00209; Kaczmarczyk, Alexander (Case 24)
    Continuing Education Lecture Series. Copies may be ordered through Alumni House.
  - Studying for and taking Exams, given by Bobbie Knable, 1978-11-02; UA136.004.024.00210; Knable, Bobbie (Case 24)
  - New Writing and Extremism in Britain Between the Wars, given by Bernard McCabe, 1978-11-16; UA136.004.024.00211; Mccabe, Bernard (Case 24)
    Symposium: Politics and Literature in the Interwar Period
  - Dress rehearsal for Terrorism in the 1920's, given by Franklin L. Ford, 1978-11-16; UA136.004.024.00212; Ford, Franklin L. (Case 24)
    Symposium: Politics and Literature In the Interwar Period
  - Mass Death and Brutalization in the First World War, given by George L. Mosse, 1978-11-16; UA136.004.024.00213; Mosse, George L. (Case 24)
  - Literary Scene in the Americas: L. Trilling & Contemporaries, given by William M. Chace, 1978-11-17; UA136.004.024.00214; Chace, William M. (Case 24)
  - The Intellectual Impact of World War I, given by David L. Schalk, 1978-11-17; UA136.004.024.00215; Schalk, David L. (Case 24)
  - Latin America Between the Wars, given by Hewson A. Ryan, 1978-11-17; UA136.004.024.00216; Ryan, Hewson A. (Case 24)
  - Gartenlaube, given by Peter Gay, 1978-11-17; UA136.004.024.00217; Gay, Peter (Case 24)
  - Popular Music of the 1920's: The European Scene, given by Ernst Halperin, 1978-11-17; UA136.004.024.00218; Halperin, Ernst (Case 24)
  - Comparative Analysis of Arthur Koestler and Victor Serge, given by Daniel Mulholland, 1978-11-17; UA136.004.024.00219 (Case 24)
  - The Alfred Stieglitz Circle, Fine Arts Symposium, 1 of 4, 1979-02-24; UA136.004.024.00220; Doty, Robert M.; Pollack, Elizabeth (Case 24)
  - The Alfred Stieglitz Circle, Fine Arts Symposium, 2 of 4, 1979-02-24; UA136.004.024.00221; Homer, William (Case 24)
  - The Alfred Stieglitz Circle, Fine Arts Symposium, 3 of 4, 1979-02-24; UA136.004.024.00222; Peters, Sarah; Rosenbloom, Naomi (Case 24)
  - The Alfred Stieglitz Circle, Fine Arts Symposium, 4 of 4, 1979-02-24; UA136.004.024.00223; Greenough, Sara (Case 24)
  - Human Rights, given by Coretta Scott King, 1979-03-23; UA136.004.024.00224; King, Coretta Scott (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - Problems of Right Conduct for Lawyers, 1 of 2, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00225; Meserve, Robert; Barshak, Edward; Freedman, Monroe; Wasserstrom, Richard (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - Problems of Right Conduct for Lawyers, 2 of 2, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00226; Meserve, Robert; Barshak, Edward; Freedman, Monroe; Wasserstrom, Richard (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - Ethical perplexities: Case studies, 1 of 2, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00227; Coquillette, Daniel R.; Lieberman, Jethro K.; Held, Virginia P. (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - Ethical perplexities: Case studies, 2 of 2, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00228; Coquillette, Daniel R.; Lieberman, Jethro K.; Held, Virginia P. (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - The A.B.A. Code of Professional Ethics, 1 of 2, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00229; Folch-Pi, Willa; Coquillette, Daniel R.; Held, Virginia P. (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - The A.B.A. Code of Professional Ethics, 2 of 2, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00230; Folch-Pi, Willa; Coquillette, Daniel R.; Held, Virginia P. (Case 24)
  - Legal Ethics and Professional Responsibility symposium - Legal and Moral Issues in Human Experimentation, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00231; Wasserstrom, Richard A. (Case 24)
  - Careers in Broadcasting career panel, 1979-03-28; UA136.004.024.00232 (Case 24)
    Career Guidance and Placement Series
  - Careers in Consulting career panel, 1979-03-29; UA136.004.024.00233 (Case 24)
  - Careers in Health Services career panel, 1979-04-04; UA136.004.024.00234 (Case 24)
  - Careers In Advertising and Public Relations career panel, 1979-04-07; UA136.004.024.00235 (Case 24)
  - Careers in Publishing and Editing career panel, 1979-04-09; UA136.004.024.00236 (Case 24)
  - General Remarks, given by John A. Volpe, 1 of 2, 1979-04-25; UA136.004.024.00237; Volpe, John A. (Case 24)
    Former Governor of Mass.; Former Ambassador to Italy. Sponsored by the Italian Society.
  - General Remarks, given by John A. Volpe, 2 of 2, 1979-04-25; UA136.004.024.00238; Volpe, John A. (Case 24)
  - Running Wall and Other Projects, given by Christo, 1979-05-07; UA136.004.024.00239 (Case 24)
  - Tufts Traditions, given by Professor R. Robbins, 1979-05-18; UA136.004.024.00240; Robbins, R. (Case 24)
  - Remarks, given by William Colby, 1979-10-11; UA136.004.024.00241; Colby, William (Case 24)
    Former Director, CIA
  - Lying: Moral Choice in Public and Private Life, given by Sissela Bok, 1979-10-22; UA136.004.024.00242; Bok, Sissela (Case 24)
    Religion Department Colloquium. Melcher Book Award presentation
  - Tufts Center for European Studies, given by Seymour Simches, 1979-10-27; UA136.004.024.00243; Simches, Seymour (Case 24)
  - Health Care Needs and Distributive Justice, given by Norman Daniels, 1979-11-02; UA136.004.024.00244; Daniels, Norman (Case 24)
  - Measurement of Blood Alcohol, given by Dr. David N. Hume, 1979-11-07; UA136.004.024.00245; Hume, David N. (Case 24)
  - Basketball: Boston Celtics, given by Arnold "Red" Auerbach, 1979-11-14; UA136.004.024.00246; Auerbach, Arnold "Red" (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
  - Public Education on World Hunger panel - Oxfam America, 1 of 2, 1979-11-15; UA136.004.024.00247 (Case 24)
  - Public Education on World Hunger panel - Oxfam America, 2 of 2, 1979-11-15; UA136.004.024.00248 (Case 24)
  - Tufts or Whatever, given by Dean Bernard Harleston, 1979-11-16; UA136.004.024.00249; Harleston, Bernard (Case 24)
  - What Students can do for Society, given by Ralph Nader, 1 of 2, 1979-11-30; UA136.004.024.00250; Nader, Ralph (Case 24)
  - What Students can do for Society, given by Ralph Nader, 2 of 2, 1979-11-30; UA136.004.024.00251; Nader, Ralph (Case 24)
  - Tufts Community Roasts Dean Harleston, 1 of 2, 1979-12-07; UA136.004.024.00252; Harleston, Bernard (Dean) (Case 24)
  - Tufts Community Roasts Dean Harleston, 2 of 2, 1979-12-07; UA136.004.024.00253; Harleston, Bernard (Dean) (Case 24)
  - American Society, given by Dick Gregory, 1 of 2, 1979-12-08; UA136.004.024.00254; Gregory, Dick (Case 24)
  - American Society, given by Dick Gregory, 2 of 2, 1979-12-08; UA136.004.024.00255; Gregory, Dick (Case 24)
  - The Cosmic Distance Scale, given by L.W. Frederick, 1979-12-09; UA136.004.024.00256; Frederick, L.W. (Case 24)
  - 1980 Presidential Campaign, given by John Anderson, 1980-02-01; UA136.004.024.00257; Anderson, John (Case 24)
  - 1980 Presidential Campaign, given by Jerry Brown, 1980-02-01; UA136.004.024.00258; Brown, Jerry (Case 24)
    Governor of California
  - Working Women: Issues and Options career panel, 1980-02-13; UA136.004.024.00259 (Case 24)
  - Computer Careers career panel, 1980-02-27; UA136.004.024.00260 (Box data_value_missing_e9cd1be6ae1288363a7130fe97883a48)
  - El Salvador Debate, given by John McAward, 1980-03-18; UA136.004.024.00261; McAward, John (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker: Samuel Barleit, U.S. Consul
  - El Salvador Debate, given by Samuel Bartleit, 1 of 2, 1980-03-18; UA136.004.024.00262; Bartleit, Samuel (Case 24)
    Co-Speaker: John McAward, Unitarian-Universalist Commission
  - Socialism, given by Michael Harrington, 1 of 2, 1980-03-19; UA136.004.024.00263; Harrington, Michael (Case 24)
  - Socialism, given by Michael Harrington, 2 of 2, 1980-03-19; UA136.004.024.00264; Harrington, Michael (Case 24)
  - Minority Careers career panel, 1980-03-19; UA136.004.024.00265 (Case 24)
  - Have Democracy and Capitalism Reached a Parting of Ways?, given by Sam Bolles, 1980-03-20; UA136.004.024.00266; Bolles, Sam (Case 24)
    Radical Economist, University of Massachusetts
  - Autobiographical and General Remarks, given by Isaac Asimov, 1980-04-17; UA136.004.024.00267; Asimov, Isaac (Case 24)
  - Physician Responsibility in a Changing Health Care System symposium: Changing Concept of Physician Responsibility, 1 of 2, 1980-04-20; UA136.004.024.00268 (Case 24)
    Sponsor: Philosophy Department. A.S. Relman, M.D., N.E. Journal of Medicine; D. Wikler, U. Wisc.
  - Physician Responsibility in a Changing Health Care System symposium: Changing Concept of Physician Responsibility, 2 of 2, 1980-04-20; UA136.004.024.00269 (Case 24)
  - Physician Responsibility in a Changing Health Care System symposium: Cost Constraints and Physician Responsibility, 1 of 2, 1980-04-20; UA136.004.024.00270 (Case 24)
    Sponsor: Philosophy Department. A. Caplan, Hastings Center Inst.; T. Delbanco, M.D., Harvard Med. School; R. Dickman, M.D., Case Western Reserve; M. Weinstein, Kennedy School Govt., Harvard School Public Health
  - Physician Responsibility in a Changing Health Care System symposium: Cost Constraints and Physician Responsibility, 2 of 2, 1980-04-20; UA136.004.024.00271 (Case 24)
  - Physician Responsibility in a Changing Health Care System symposium: Distribution of Physicians and Physician Responsibility, 1 of 2, 1980-04-20; UA136.004.024.00272 (Case 24)